<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Rajekevin</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 11:35:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill 8080</title>
      <link>/kill-8080/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 11:35:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kill-8080/</guid>
      <description>If you are using Windows, it&#39;s can be useful to kill certain port. I will show you, how to kill the process :
netstat -ano | findstr :8080 taskkill /PID typeyourPIDhere </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blur</title>
      <link>/blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 16:20:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blur/</guid>
      <description>What is Blur function in jQuery ?It is used to remove focus from the selected elements.
Code
$(selector).blur(function) For more information Click here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Read#2</title>
      <link>/friday-read-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:34:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/friday-read-2/</guid>
      <description>This Friday Read#2 is dedicated to : https://dev.to/
Best website to all article related to software development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ip Spoofing</title>
      <link>/ip-spoofing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 09:53:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ip-spoofing/</guid>
      <description>IP Spoofing is the process of replacing the source IP address with a fake IP address from the IP packets to hide the real identity of the sender.
The source address is the address of the computer that the packet an attacker can make it appear that the packet an attacker can make it appear that the packet was sent by a different computer system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implement Firewall</title>
      <link>/implement-firewall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 18:10:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/implement-firewall/</guid>
      <description>Why should I implement firewall ?It prevents unauthorized users from accessing protected network resources.
We can use two methods for implementing firewalls:
 Packet filtering firewall (ACL) Stateful firewall (a network firewall that tracks the operating state and characteristics of network connections traversing it)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAA Protocol</title>
      <link>/aaa-protocol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 17:49:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aaa-protocol/</guid>
      <description>The authentication, authorization, and accounting (AAA) is a protocol for enabling administrative access. AAA controls who is allowed to connect to the network, what they are allowed to do, and tracks records of what was done.
In small or simple networks, AAA authentication can be implemented using the local database. However, in larger or complex networks, AAA authentication should be implemented using server-based AAA. AAA servers can use RADIUS or TACACS+ protocols to communicate with client routers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Network Security Threats</title>
      <link>/network-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 19:05:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/network-security/</guid>
      <description>We can see a lot of kinds of threats, like viruses, worms, and Trojan.A virus is malicious software attached to another program to execute unwanted actions on an end system. A worm executes arbitrary code and installs copies of itself in the memory of an infected computer, which then infects other hosts. A Trojan horse is an application that was written to look like something else.
In addition to these types of threats, there are other categories of threats, such as Reconnaissance attacks &amp;amp; DoS attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday Read#1</title>
      <link>/friday-read-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 19:35:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/friday-read-1/</guid>
      <description>I would like to present you a beautiful website : https://css-tricks.com/ design by Kylie Timpani &amp;amp; Chris Coyier.
This new design looks awesome ! This website shows you all the tricks for Front-End Developpers or all the people who love coding in CSS
All the article well very documented, with the sample of code to reproduce the step. Very useful, if you want to develop your front-end skills!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Bye PHP5 😥</title>
      <link>/php5-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 20:07:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php5-end/</guid>
      <description>14 years of love story with PHP5, now finish, since the new year 2019 ! I started, learned, praticed with this version of PHP. Now PHP5, since December 31, 2018, security support for PHP 5.6.x is officially cease ; marking the end of all support for any version of the ancient PHP 5.x branch 😥
It exposes hundreds of millions of websites (who still running on PHP 5.x version), to serious security risks ☠️.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Render Html Tags</title>
      <link>/render-html-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 19:45:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/render-html-tags/</guid>
      <description>When you store HTML tags in your database, you would like to retrieve these datas as HTML Content, not a string right ?
&amp;lt;?php echo $row[&amp;#39;description&amp;#39;]; ?&amp;gt;` Maybe when you want to display this data, it show as a string character : &amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hello, I am PHP&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt; Don&#39;t worry, call your best elePHPhant 🐘 and use htmlspecialchars_decode()
 The htmlspecialchars() function converts some predefined characters to HTML entities
 &amp;lt;?php echo htmlspecialchars($row[&amp;#39;description&amp;#39;]); ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s 2019 Begin</title>
      <link>/lets-2019-begin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:15:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lets-2019-begin/</guid>
      <description>Yeah first post of the year. Let me wish you a Happy New Year.Big project, big work, big ambition, this year will be exciting!
That&#39;s the kinda thing, I&#39;m gonna to do&amp;hellip;
 With Great power comes great responsibility&amp;hellip;
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>